Inexperienced
heartless,
but even so,
Be Beautiful
No Destiny, unworthy
If we just talk as if it's never enough
“If it's like this, then probably things will go well”
Things, money, love,words,
I'm tired of self-asserting myself already
Déjà vu, what are you so unsatisfied about？
You've said all sorts of selfish things.
What more could you possibly want？
But surprise, I don't hate this situation.
Already,
"I'm sick of hearing that line"
The one thing I don't want is ambiguousness!
Enough!
Even if you say to do this or that,
Even if you say love me, or why?
It's easy if it's just for fun.
And that it's reckless serious negotiating
Those contemptuous and surprising words.
How many times do you want to use?
Anyway,
I was hoping it even in a fixed game,
Even all those quoted phrases,
The words make people tiptoe.
let these things become taboo.
Take a hint, don't let it rain.
I hate talking in a roundabout way.
If you must speak,
"Answer it within two words."
Red butterfly, even a letter can not be served
Spreading a  fragile folding fan.
That is more attractive, isn't it?
Confused.
If you can't answer, please leave me alone.
If you can't stop hesitating, please leave me.
The key words, but you don't listen.
If it is only for the sake of peace of mind and then fall...
Sweet raindrops.
You also want to hold up the umbrella, right？
Like this,
I hope I can always look forward to it.
I closed my eyes.
I wanted to change.
Pretending to be an adult.
Lost.
But things are irreparable.
Now, please don't stop raining.
Copy,
Paste,
Delete.
Repeat these actions.
Breathe in,
Breathe out.
So, ah…
Even so...It doesn't matter,
this is a heartache love!
That's enough!!
Even if you say to do this or that,
Even if you say love me, or why?
It's easy if it's just for fun.
And that it's fragmented serious negotiating
Those contemptuous and heavy lies (truth).
Let these things all become taboo.
(Request tone) Surely ,
We were hoping anyway, even if it was a fixed race,
Even the words that are said in the official cavity'
And the habit of picking up your toes,
quit these habits together.
Take a hint, don't let it clear up.
It is also rainy today.
Collapse the umbrella.
Going home in the rain.